{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Fraud Awareness Month ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz to test your knowledge.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18452","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18470","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_166","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_166","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si18452","si18470","Text_Caption_106","Image_166"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_148","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  What things can help you defend against cybersecurity threats? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Update software regularly ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Update software regularly\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12371","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_330","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Keep different passwords for different accounts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12371_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"177","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Keep different passwords for different accounts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Learn how to recognise scams such as phishing emails ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Learn how to recognise scams such as phishing emails\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17932","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the Above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17932_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the Above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18797","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19029","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19042","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19057","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19085","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19098","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19113","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19126","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Setting regular updates, creating different passwords and learning about frauds may seem boring, but it is very important to maintain.  Many scams rely on people taking shortcuts to their cybersecurity preparedness.  Make a habit of changing your passwords and maintaining your knowledge of good cybersecurity practices.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Setting regular updates, creating different passwords and learning about frauds may seem boring, but it is very important to maintain.  Many scams rely on people taking shortcuts to their cybersecurity preparedness.  Make a habit of changing your passwords and maintaining your knowledge of good cybersecurity practices.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_148","si12349","si12364","si12375","si12386","si17936","si12459","si12473","si18783","si18797","si19029","si19042","si19057","si19070","si19085","si19098","si19113","si19126","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  What things can help you defend against cybersecurity threats?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_149","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_149","roles":{}},{"id":"si16169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_580","roles":{}},{"id":"si16077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_569","title":"2.  Who and what is impacted if my computer is breached by a cybersecurity attack? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_570","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_571","title":"Myself and my devices, and my accounts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"322","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Myself and my devices, and my accounts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16099","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_572","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_573","title":"Devices linked to my devices ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16099_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"324","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Devices linked to my devices\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20009","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"My contacts ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20009_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"My contacts\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20039","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20043","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20039_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_579","roles":{}},{"id":"si16187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18811","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18825","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19141","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19154","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19169","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19182","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19210","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19225","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19238","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_576","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  When hackers and scammers try to compromise your security and infect your devices, they aren’t always targeting just you.  Hackers can use your infected devices and accounts to infect other linked devices . Sometimes hackers use compromised accounts to abuse trusted relationships in order to infect more systems. When we all secure our systems, we make each other safer.  Make sure to secure your accounts and devices for everyone’s sake. e best policy. Avoid ‘save my password’ or ‘remember me’ offers.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_577","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  When hackers and scammers try to compromise your security and infect your devices, they aren’t always targeting just you.  Hackers can use your infected devices and accounts to infect other linked devices . Sometimes hackers use compromised accounts to abuse trusted relationships in order to infect more systems. When we all secure our systems, we make each other safer.  Make sure to secure your accounts and devices for everyone’s sake. .  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_578","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16211","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_149","si16077","si16092","si16103","si20013","si20043","si16187","si16201","si18811","si18825","si19141","si19154","si19169","si19182","si19197","si19210","si19225","si19238","si16157"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16211"},"question":{"interactionId":"16057","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.  Who and what is impacted if my computer is breached by a cybersecurity attack?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_150","roles":{}},{"id":"si16375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_594","roles":{}},{"id":"si16272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_581","title":"3.  What can I expect from news and messages I get through social media? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_582","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_583","title":"Trusted content from the people and organizations I subscribe to ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"329","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Trusted content from the people and organizations I subscribe to\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_584","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_585","title":"Random content from all over the internet that could be anything ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16294_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"331","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Random content from all over the internet that could be anything\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20219","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20223","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Targeted content from advertisers and political groups that is meant to influence my behavior ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20219_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Targeted content from advertisers and political groups that is meant to influence my behavior\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20238","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A mix of all three ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20234_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A mix of all three\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_593","roles":{}},{"id":"si16393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18839","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18853","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19266","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19281","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19309","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19322","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19350","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_590","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Our social media networks are more open than we would often expect.  We will get content directly from the people and organizations you subscribe to, but a lot of content has been repeated from other sources.  Some content will pass your way at random, some content has been designed to get your attention and sway your buying decisions or political leanings. Browse your social media with a critical-eye so that you can tell what is real and what isn’t.  If you aren’t sure about something, double-check it from a different source.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_591","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Our social media networks are more open than we would often expect.  We will get content directly from the people and organizations you subscribe to, but a lot of content has been repeated from other sources.  Some content will pass your way at random, some content has been designed to get your attention and sway your buying decisions or political leanings. Browse your social media with a critical-eye so that you can tell what is real and what isn’t.  If you aren’t sure about something, double-check it from a different source.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_592","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16417","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_150","si16272","si16287","si16298","si20223","si20238","si16393","si16407","si18839","si18853","si19253","si19266","si19281","si19294","si19309","si19322","si19337","si19350","si16363"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16417"},"question":{"interactionId":"16252","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  What can I expect from news and messages I get through social media?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_151","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_151","roles":{}},{"id":"si16536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_604","roles":{}},{"id":"si16455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_595","title":"4.  What can you expect from bitcoin transactions? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_596","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_597","title":"Bitcoin transactions are completely safe and transparent  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"338","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bitcoin transactions are completely safe and transparent \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_598","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_599","title":"It has the potential to be used for scams and frauds just like any other currency ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"340","roles":{"answer":{"title":"It has the potential to be used for scams and frauds just like any other currency\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si17445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Bitcoin is a shady currency that should never be trusted under any circumstance ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17445_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bitcoin is a shady currency that should never be trusted under any circumstance\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_603","roles":{}},{"id":"si16554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_84","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18867","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18881","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19365","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19393","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19434","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19462","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_600","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  While there is a large legal market for safe and transparent bitcoin transactions, it is not universally safe. Scammers have found ways of using bitcoin for criminal tricks. Many scams try to get people to send bitcoin in fake transactions.  Before going into a bitcoin exchange, ask yourself a few questions: Am I sure I’m sending this to a person I can trust? Would I expect to be sending bitcoin for something like this?  While many institutions are exploring ways of using the technologies behind bitcoin, no official service will demand payment in bitcoin. Think before you send anything. It could be a scam.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_601","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  While there is a large legal market for safe and transparent bitcoin transactions, it is not universally safe. Scammers have found ways of using bitcoin for criminal tricks. Many scams try to get people to send bitcoin in fake transactions.  Before going into a bitcoin exchange, ask yourself a few questions: Am I sure I’m sending this to a person I can trust? Would I expect to be sending bitcoin for something like this?  While many institutions are exploring ways of using the technologies behind bitcoin, no official service will demand payment in bitcoin. Think before you send anything. It could be a scam.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_602","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16578","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_151","si16455","si16470","si16481","si17449","si16554","si16568","si18867","si18881","si19365","si19378","si19393","si19406","si19421","si19434","si19449","si19462","si16524"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16578"},"question":{"interactionId":"16435","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.  What can you expect from bitcoin transactions?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_152","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_152","roles":{}},{"id":"si16697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_614","roles":{}},{"id":"si16616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_605","title":"5. You may have already received a call from “Microsoft” or “Apple” saying your computer has a virus and they can fix it for you (for a cost). What suggests this is a telemarketing scam? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_606","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_607","title":"They persist no matter what you say ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"343","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They persist no matter what you say\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_608","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_609","title":"You did not report a problem with your computer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"345","roles":{"answer":{"title":"You did not report a problem with your computer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17475","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17479","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"“Microsoft” would not phone individual users ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17475_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"“Microsoft” would not phone individual users\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18035","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18039","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18035_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_613","roles":{}},{"id":"si16715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18895","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18909","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19490","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19505","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19518","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19546","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19561","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_610","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  The Computer Virus Telemarketing Scam has convinced many people to pay for an unnecessary and fake computer fix out of fear. They usually direct a person to a website to make a payment and download an anti-virus fix which is a hoax. If you have concerns about your computer, talk to someone you trust, and never give out banking or personal information on an unsolicited call.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_611","title":"Incorrect -Answer:  D  The Computer Virus Telemarketing Scam has convinced many people to pay for an unnecessary and fake computer fix out of fear. They usually direct a person to a website to make a payment and download an anti-virus fix which is a hoax. If you have concerns about your computer, talk to someone you trust, and never give out banking or personal information on an unsolicited call.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_612","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16739","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_152","si16616","si16631","si16642","si17479","si18039","si16715","si16729","si18895","si18909","si19477","si19490","si19505","si19518","si19533","si19546","si19561","si19574","si16685"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16739"},"question":{"interactionId":"16596","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. You may have already received a call from “Microsoft” or “Apple” saying your computer has a virus and they can fix it for you (for a cost). What suggests this is a telemarketing scam?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_153","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_153","roles":{}},{"id":"si16858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_624","roles":{}},{"id":"si16777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_615","title":"6.  You receive a message giving you the good news that you won a vacation and need to phone a number to claim the prize. Is this a scam? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_616","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_617","title":"Yes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"348","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Yes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_618","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_619","title":"No ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16799_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"350","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_623","roles":{}},{"id":"si16876","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18923","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18937","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19602","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19617","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19630","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19673","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19686","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16822","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_620","title":"Correct -Answer:  A  The Unclaimed Prize Scam lures people into calling the number and giving personal and credit card information to “secure the winnings”. There is no prize.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16834","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_621","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  The Unclaimed Prize Scam lures people into calling the number and giving personal and credit card information to “secure the winnings”. There is no prize.    Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_622","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16900","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_153","si16777","si16792","si16803","si16876","si16890","si18923","si18937","si19589","si19602","si19617","si19630","si19645","si19658","si19673","si19686","si16846"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16900"},"question":{"interactionId":"16757","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  You receive a message giving you the good news that you won a vacation and need to phone a number to claim the prize. Is this a scam?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_154","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_154","roles":{}},{"id":"si17049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_636","roles":{}},{"id":"si16957","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_625","title":"7. The Internet has opened up a world of tempting things to buy online. These sites are even advertised on TV. Can I get a real Gucci handbag or Rolex watch (or my prescription drug) at a great price online? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_626","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_627","title":"No, you get what you pay for ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"353","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No, you get what you pay for\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_628","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_629","title":"Sure, because they don’t have to run a store ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"355","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Sure, because they don’t have to run a store\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_635","roles":{}},{"id":"si17067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_91","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18951","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18965","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19701","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19714","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19729","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19742","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19757","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19770","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19785","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19798","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_632","title":"Correct -Answer:  A  The Counterfeit Merchandise Scam has flourished because the Internet is filled with online stores and auction sites marketing alluring, cheaply priced, counterfeit products (including medications and other drugs), which are pitched as the real thing. Know the difference between a real and a fake, and remember that if it sounds too good to be true, it usually is.    Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_633","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  A  The Counterfeit Merchandise Scam has flourished because the Internet is filled with online stores and auction sites marketing alluring, cheaply priced, counterfeit products (including medications and other drugs), which are pitched as the real thing. Know the difference between a real and a fake, and remember that if it sounds too good to be true, it usually is.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_634","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17091","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_154","si16957","si16972","si16983","si17067","si17081","si18951","si18965","si19701","si19714","si19729","si19742","si19757","si19770","si19785","si19798","si17037"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17091"},"question":{"interactionId":"16937","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. The Internet has opened up a world of tempting things to buy online. These sites are even advertised on TV. Can I get a real Gucci handbag or Rolex watch (or my prescription drug) at a great price online?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_155","roles":{}},{"id":"si17225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_648","roles":{}},{"id":"si17133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_637","title":"8.  Dating on the internet can open up both opportunities and dangers. What kind of behaviour in online dating could indicate that someone is a scammer? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_638","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_639","title":"When they use bad spelling, too many emojis, or send unsolicited photos ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360","roles":{"answer":{"title":"When they use bad spelling, too many emojis, or send unsolicited photos\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_640","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_641","title":"If they insist on meeting right away and don’t want to talk online ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17155_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362","roles":{"answer":{"title":"If they insist on meeting right away and don’t want to talk online\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18095","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18099","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"If they keep making excuses not to meet in-person but they are asking for money ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18095_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"If they keep making excuses not to meet in-person but they are asking for money\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si18110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18114","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18110_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_647","roles":{}},{"id":"si17243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18993","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19826","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19841","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19854","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19869","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19882","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19897","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19910","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_644","title":"Correct -Answer:  C  There are many diverse people on the internet who are strange, quirky or just unsavoury, but they aren’t necessarily trying to scam you.  There are two main things that can signify that someone is trying to scam you: they won’t provide anything that is personally identifying (real name, in-person visits, birthdate, address), and that they want to involve you in a financial transaction somehow (sending money, asking you to move around goods, etc…). They will do and say anything to get you to do what they want without divulging their own personal information.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_645","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  There are many diverse people on the internet who are strange, quirky or just unsavoury, but they aren’t necessarily trying to scam you.  There are two main things that can signify that someone is trying to scam you: they won’t provide anything that is personally identifying (real name, in-person visits, birthdate, address), and that they want to involve you in a financial transaction somehow (sending money, asking you to move around goods, etc…). They will do and say anything to get you to do what they want without divulging their own personal information.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_646","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17267","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_155","si17133","si17148","si17159","si18099","si18114","si17243","si17257","si18979","si18993","si19813","si19826","si19841","si19854","si19869","si19882","si19897","si19910","si17213"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17267"},"question":{"interactionId":"17113","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  Dating on the internet can open up both opportunities and dangers. What kind of behaviour in online dating could indicate that someone is a scammer?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_120","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19925","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19938","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19953","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19966","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_121","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Animation_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Animation_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18490","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si18504","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Image_121","Button_4","si18490","si18504","Text_Caption_5"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"March2018Quiz","class":"project","title":"March2018Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide12483","Slide16211","Slide16417","Slide16578","Slide16739","Slide16900","Slide17091","Slide17267","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide16211q1","Slide16417q2","Slide16578q3","Slide16739q4","Slide16900q5","Slide17091q6","Slide17267q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide16211","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16417","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide16578","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16739","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide16900","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17091","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17267","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}